<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NetbeeTest</string>
    <string name="main_title">Últimas notícias</string>
    <string name="load_message">Carregando informações…</string>
    <string name="load_title">Aguarde…</string>
    <string name="message_error_dialog">Não foi possível carregar as informações!</string>
    <string name="agree">Ok</string>
    <string name="empty_message">Nenhuma notícia para mostrar</string>
    <string name="news_title">Comentários</string>
    <string name="example_html_text">##Conclusion##\\n_\\n\\n##HTC U11 Bottom line##\\n\\nWhen I reviewed the U Ultra, I could see the potential in the design and hardware execution — that phone was just unfortunately saddled with multiple issues including its size, a couple bad internal spec choices, a subpar camera and a far-too-high price. HTC has remedied nearly all of those issues just a couple months later with the U11. It has a more manageable size, ditched the second screen, improved battery life, overhauled the camera and lowered the price to $649.\\n\\nIf the U11 doesn\'t sell well, it will have nothing to do with the outright quality of the phone itself.\\nWith those issues out of the way you can appreciate what a beautiful phone the U11 is, with a design that\'s truly unique to look at and solid to hold. You can also appreciate the ridiculous speed, fluidity and consistency of the software that beats everything but Google\'s own phone. And if you\'re a fan of the spartan approach to features and apps as I am, you\'ll like what HTC is doing here. Even if the interface isn\'t demonstrably changed from two years ago, at least the design is solid and you\'re not saddled with tons of cruft that\'s constantly in your way.\\n\\nI don\'t think anyone was expecting HTC to come out swinging with a flagship smartphone that can steal a large number of sales from the big names out there, particularly in North America and Western Europe. But if the U11 doesn\'t sell well in 2017, it will have nothing to do with the outright quality of the phone itself. It\'s a really great phone that does so much right with so few missteps along the way. HTC has just lost so much ground in market share and brand awareness that it\'s fighting an uphill battle no matter what it puts out.\\n\\nThe U11 has everything it needs to be a challenger to the top crop of phones in the market today — now HTC just needs people to get to the point of giving its phones a chance again.\\\"</string>
    <string name="empty_comment">Nenhum comentário aqui</string>
</resources>
